EMIL MADSEN

emilmiliam@outlook.com • linkedin.com/in/emil-madsen-7400a6222/ • github.com/Nesstark

ABOUT

I am a 22-year-old student studying Medialogy at Aalborg University in Copenhagen, with experience as an administrative sales assistant at Snevagten. In my role, I have developed my collaboration skills and the ability to thrive in a corporate culture where teamwork is essential for success.

In addition to my administrative skills, I have in-depth technical expertise, particularly with Windows computers. I am also interested in photography and drones and I often spend my free time improving my skills in these areas.

EDUCATION

Aalborg University in Copenhagen

Started August 2023

Medialogy

Slotshaven Gymnasium

Graduation June 2020

Study programme: Mathmatics and Physics

Elective courses: Social Science B, Psychology C, Astronomy C

SKILLS

Design and modeling tools: SketchUp, Revit, AutoCAD, Microsoft Office

Programming: HTML, CSS, C#, C++
Data analysis and statistics: Excel

EXPERIENCE

Snevagten A/S, Administrative Sales Assistant

Maj 2022 - Now

Assisting the sales team in the company with administrative tasks.

School (Bramsnæsvigskolen), Substitute teacher

Sep 2021 - Feb 2022

· Substitute teacher for grades 1 through 9.

Kindergarden (Børnehuset Holbæk Have), Pedagogical assistant

Dec 2020 - Maj 2021

• Full-time pedagogical assistant, with a focus on a single classroom.

Kvickly, Sales assistant

Jun 2017 - Jan 2021

· Sales assistant and closing manager.

OTHER SKILLS

Design: Lightroom, Photoshop,

Miscellaneous: Word, PowerPoint, Windows

PERSONAL

Languages

Danish: Fluent (Native Language), English: High level

Certificates

Drivers license, Diploma

Free time

Often used on my hobbies, photography, computers and time with my family